Ukwuoma Tochukwu

Owerri Municipal, Imo, Nigeria

ukwuomatochi112@gmail.com

08169039269

linkedin.com/in/ukwuoma-tochukwu

Summary

I'm a software developer specializing in front-end web development.

I design and build highly responsive web pages and web applications with great user experience. I'm a creative person and that plays a good role in my work.

So far, I have HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript, Bootstrap, JQuery, ReactJS, MySgl, PHP, and Git/GitHub in my skill set.

I'm still enthusiastically learning other frameworks and programming languages on the go.

I have led a team of developers during my internships with different companies in delivering tasks efficiently.

I'm always open to learning and improving my skills.

Experience

SidoHustio ReactJS Developer

Side Hustle

Apr 2022 - Jul 2022 (4 months)

As a react developer intern at Side hustle, I learned and applied ReactJS in building responsive web pages and applications.

I led a team of five interns in carrying out tasks effectively and delivering within the time given.

It was a nice experience.

Full-stack Developer

Anhydraze

Feb 2022 - Jul 2022 (6 months)

During this period of training, I learned the basics of frontend and backend development using ReactJS and Laravel in the respective tracks.

I contributed to building the company's official website as a backend developer.

Student Intern

Oluaka Institute of Technology

Sep 2021 - Jan 2022 (5 months)

I learned the basics of frontend web development and how to use the version control system, GitHub.

Education



👖 Nnamdi Azikiwe University

Bachelor of Science - BS, Mathematics Oct 2018 - Nov 2023

Licenses & Certifications

React Js - Side Hustle SH-IT-0033635

- Soft skill training Jobberman Youth Engagement & Learning
- Technical Support Fundamentals Coursera CWRQNZKP97ZZ

Skills

Cascading Style Sheets (CSS) • Bootstrap • Laravel • JavaScript • PHP • MySQL • Git • React.js • HTML5 • Communication